<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>CSH for image tooltips</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_imagetooltips_tooltip</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="related_image_position.description">The position (starting from zero) of the image in the related content element for which this tooltip should be displayed</label>
			<label index="tooltip_text.description">The text that will be shown as tooltip for the specified image</label>
			<label index="tooltip_position_x.description">Horizontal position of the Tooltip relative to the related content element</label>>
			<label index="tooltip_position_y.description">Vertical position of the Tooltip relative to the related content element</label>>
			<label index="tooltip_offset_x.description">Offset of Tooltip in horizontal direction in pixels, seen from left (may be negative). Remember the GAP!</label>
			<label index="tooltip_offset_y.description">Offset of Tooltip in vertical direction in pixels, seen from above (may be negative). Remember the GAP!</label>
			<label index="tooltip_opacity.description">Opacity of Tooltip in % (0 .. 100 allowed, default 100)</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="related_content_element.description">Das Inhaltselement, für das dieser Tooltip angezeigt werden soll</label>
			<label index="related_image_position.description">Position (beginnend bei 0) des Bildes innerhalb des gewählten Inhaltselements für das dieser Tooltip angezeigt werden soll.</label>
			<label index="tooltip_text.description">Der Text, der als Tooltip angezeigt wird.</label>
			<label index="tooltip_position_x.description">Horizontale Position des Tooltips relativ zum Content-Element</label>
			<label index="tooltip_position_y.description">Vertikale Position des Tooltips relativ zum Content-Element</label>
			<label index="tooltip_offset_x.description">Veschiebung des Tooltips in horizontaler Richtung in Pixeln, ausgehend von links (kann negativ sein). Denk an die LÜCKE!</label>
			<label index="tooltip_offset_y.description">Veschiebung des Tooltips in vertikaler Richtung in Pixeln, ausgehend von oben (kann negativ sein). Denk an die LÜCKE!</label>
			<label index="tooltip_opacity.description">Deckkraft (Nicht-Transparenz) des Tooltips in % (0 .. 100 erlaubt)</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>